Sergey Shutkin

Contact

Address:

Ottawa, Ontario, Canada

Email:

great.dolphin.ls@gmail.com

Skype:

great.dolphin.ls

Phone:

+1 209 730 6840

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ser gey-shutkin-3a39861ab/

Languages

English: intermediate

Summary

Senior Web Developer specializing in front end development with more than 8 years experiences. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5 and CSS, JavaScript, React, MySQL, MongoDB, PHP, Node.js, Apollo + Graphql. Have power skill in fintech web applications. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Skill Highlights

- React
- **Express**
- Node.js

- MongoDB
- Database Design
- Pixel Perfect Design

Experience

Full stack developer - 10/2019 to 05/2020, WoW, US **WoW** is a learning platform for fintech educators.

Work with designers to create large, complex design pages

- Develop backend with Express.js and Apollo + Graphql

Full stack developer - 04/2018 to 12/2019, Merit, US

Merit empowers you to make recommendations of people who you have worked with directly so they can be showcased to hiring managers. hellomerit.com

- Develop full project including frontend and backend
- Deploy it on AWS and maintenance project

Front end Developer - 12/2016 to 05/2018, Turnout Nation, US

Turnout Nation is a method, a community, and a movement of activists who commit to getting ten friends to vote. www.turnoutnation.org

- Work with senior developers to create large, complex design pages
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end

React Developer - 09/2015 to 12/2016, Flowfact AG, German

Flowfact AG is a Germany Software Company that provides information and contract about real estate. www.flowfact.de

- Cooperate with the QA tester on mobile responsive issues
- Develop a print design of a single-page depending on customers' requirements.
- Develop reusable and granular UI components

Javascript developer - 02/2012 to 09/2013, Demoreel, US

Demoreel helps actors to they build their own profile site very easily. demoreel.com

- Port Angular 1.5 project int Angular 6.0
- Develop Admin Dashboard and fix feedback from clients

Education

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING:

Shanghai University — 2007-2011

Certifications

Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3(AWS).